https://soulduster.net/privacy-policy/

Wholesale
Search for:
Website Security
At SoulDuster.net, we understands security is a concern when ordering online. That is why we use the most advanced technology for processing transactions. Our checkout pages are secure and PCI-DDS compliant, a worldwide information security standard adopted by the Payment Card Industry Security Standards Council. SoulDuster.net utilizes GeoTrust’s encryption solution with 256-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to transmit information. You can view the details as well as the current status of our Geotrust SSL Certificate by clicking on the GeoTrust logo on the bottom of our webpages.
As an added protection, your credit card information is safeguarded by the payment gateway. When you place an order online, SoulDuster.net does not receive your credit card details. Your credit card number is never stored in our databases.
Your Privacy
Protecting your privacy is very important to us. The following statement will help you understand how SoulDuster.net (the “Website”) collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us. By using the Website, you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Personal Information Collected By The Website
When you place an order on the Website, you will need to submit personal information, such as name, address, email address, and credit card information, for us to process the order and communicate order and tracking information to you.
Our email system stores our email communications to serve as references to facilitate future communications if you have additional inquiries.
You do not need an account to shop on the Website. Creating an account allows you to access features that are restricted to registered users. Examples include submitting product reviews and feedback (the “Feedback Areas”). If you wish to create an account, you will need to submit a username and password, and certain other personal data as needed. This information is used to authenticate your login. Please note that comments submitted in the Feedback Areas are public. You may elect to cancel the account later by following the opt-out procedures included with our communication to you.
Non-Personal Information Collected By The Website
The Website may collect non-personal information, such as the type of browser you are using. Such information is only used as an aggregate to help us learn about traffic patterns on our Website and opportunities to enhance user experience.
Our Website utilizes cookie technology. Cookies are “identifiers” that our Website transfers to your computer to enable our Website to recognize your browser, track the pages you have visited, provide shopping features, and store items you leave in your Shopping Cart.
Information Sharing
Information sharing on our Website is very limited and is only on an as-needed basis. SoulDuster.net utilizes ShopperApproved’s service to survey users’ experiences on our website. You will be asked to participate in the survey when you complete your checkout. A follow up survey is sent to you via email after a couple of weeks to solicit your input after you receive the order. SoulDuster.net may occasionally hire third party consultants to enhance our Website. These consultants also follow straight privacy practices.
SHOP
2021 Calendars
Note & Greeting Cards
Jigsaw Puzzles
Journals
Art Prints
Home Decor
ABOUT US
© Copyright 2003 - 2020 YUOP, Inc., DBA: SoulDuster. annie|catherine. Ultimate Nourishment. All Rights Reserved
